

Bruno Santiago Diaz Bermudez

Profile

I am currently working as a Software Evolution Engineer in Wizeline. I am very passionate about technology. Until now, I have worked in developing apps, web pages, and have some experience in video game programming, as well as in QA. I have worked with different frameworks like Shopify, React, Node.JS, Laravel. I also love healthy competition, and learning new things.

Employment History

Web developer, Glitch Corner Studios, Guadalajara

JANUARY 2018 - NOVEMBER 2018

I worked with them attending web develop related projects.

Web developer, Nostum, Guadalajara

APRIL 2019 - MAY 2021

Had a big leading role since it was a small studio and had a small team, worked in various areas like participating in data-base design, making various endpoints of Rest APIs, making One-Pages on my own from scratch in very few days for clients with React. Also having constant communication with my team and the client.

Software Evolution Engineer, Wizeline, Guadalajara

MAY 2021 - PRESENT

Started contribuing to internal project as a FrontEnd Developer with a big team, then moved to work with a client as a QA engineer despite not having worked as a QA before I quickly adapt, learnt and gave very good results, as a Squad we are doing the best of all in my current project. As a QA I became very familiar with agile metodologies and improving my comunnication with the client and every department of the team.

Education

ITESO, Guadalajara

AUGUST 2014 - JANUARY 2017

I started studying chemistry engineering, but change my career path in the third semester were I started taking software engineer related classes, I had to pause my career due to financial issues but I am still interested in finishing a software engineer career.

Details

3332488352

brunodiazb16@gmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH

16/05/1994

Skills

React

JavaScript |

HTML/CSS

Node.js

Python

PHP

Git

SQL

MongoDB

Amazon AWS

Languages

Spanish

English